IBT0061
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Story and Photo Files, Series 3
  - Story and Photo Files, December 1990, Photo [2 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, December 1990, Photos [3 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, December 1990, Photos [4 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, December 1990, Copy [1 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, December 1990, Copy [2 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, December 1990, Copy [3 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1991, Background and Original Copy [1 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1991, Background and Original Copy [2 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1991, Background and Original Copy [3 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1991, Background and Original Copy [4 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1991, Background and Original Copy [5 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1991, Background and Original Copy [6 of 6], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1991, Photos [1 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1991, Photos [2 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1991, Back Up [1 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1991, Back Up [2 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1991, Back Up [3 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1991, Back Up [4 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1991, Photos, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1991, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1991, Back Up [1 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1991, Back Up [2 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1991, Back Up [3 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1991, Back Up [4 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1991, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, April 1991, Original and Back Up Copy [1 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, April 1991, Original and Back Up Copy [2 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, April 1991, Original and Back Up Copy [3 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, April 1991, Original and Back Up Copy [4 of 4], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, April 1991 [1 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, April 1991 [2 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1991, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Teamster Video Log Sheets, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, Video Transcripts, 1991; IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, Videotape Logs, April 1991; IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, Information Packet, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1979, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1979, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1979, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, April 1979, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1979, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1979, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1979, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, August 1979, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, September 1979 [1 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, September 1979 [2 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1979 [1 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, October 1979 [2 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, November 1979, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, December 1979, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, January 1980, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1980, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Story and Photo Files, February 1980, Pay Advisory Panel, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1980 [1 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Story and Photo Files, March 1980 [2 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Story and Photo Files, April 1980, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1980 [1 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1980 [2 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Story and Photo Files, May 1980 [3 of 3], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Story and Photo Files, June 1980, IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1980 [1 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Story and Photo Files, July 1980 [2 of 2], IBT0061 Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 12)